keywordissimo.com 2014-06-29

# Keywordissimo - Keyword Analysis

Keywordissimo and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “Keywordissimo”) recognize the importance of keeping the personal information you provide to us private and secure. Keywordissimo has developed a comprehensive privacy policy and we use the latest technology to ensure that your personal information is secure. 

#### Information Collection & Use

##### General

We collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our website. Any personal, private information you provide to us will be used in connection to contact you about the products or services in which you have expressed an interest or which may be related. We do not share any information about you or your company to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to administer the communications we offer and as permitted by law. We may use a third party service provider to for communications; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. If you follow us on Twitter, Facebook or on other social media services, we may use information provided by these services to customize our communications to you. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

##### Software

With your permission, we may collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that we believe might make our products and/or services better. This anonymous information is used to improve our product offerings and make our products more relevant to you. We retain the anonymous information that we collect about you only for as long as it remains relevant. 

##### Forums

In order to use our forums, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to provide contact information (such as name and email address). We may use this information to contact you about the products or services on our site in which you have expressed interest or which may be related. You may have the option to provide additional demographic information (such as title, company size, income level, gender etc.) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site and in our marketing communications. 

##### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfil your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. We may also use this information to contact you about the products or services on our site which you have purchased or which may be related including information related to renewing your support subscription. 

##### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to better understand our customers and to tailor any information that we may send you relating to our product or services. By participating in a contest, you give us permission to publicize your name and company affiliation solely in connection with the contest. 

#### Communications from the Site

##### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on our products, services, special deals, or promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section. 

##### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section. 

##### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our Ext Designer validation service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send you an email notification. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.. Please see “Choice and Opt-out.” 

##### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we may send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

##### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and third party tracking services such as Google Analytics to create a “profile” of your preferences. We may tie your personally identifiable information and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

##### Supplementation of Information

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

##### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may share aggregated demographic and survey information about our user base with our partners. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

##### Agents

We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

##### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website 

##### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at newsletter@Keywordissimo.com 

##### Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to identify defects, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. IP addresses may be tied to personally identifiable information to identify your location or similar characteristics. We use a third-party tracking service that may use cookies, log files, or other technologies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We may link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We may use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site. Some of our business partners (e.g., our analytics provider) may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by us only and does not cover the use of cookies by any such firm. 

##### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.” 

##### Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Keywordissimo. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

##### Forums

If you use our Forums, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Although the administrators and moderators of Keywordissimo Forums will attempt to keep all objectionable messages off, it is impossible for us to review all messages. All messages express the views of the author, and the owners of Keywordissimo Forums will be not held responsible for the content of any message. As a member of the Keywordissimo Forums, you warrant that you will not post any messages that are obscene, vulgar, sexually-oriented, hateful, threatening, or otherwise violate any laws. We reserve the right to remove, edit, move or close any content item for any reason. 

##### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can send email us. 

##### Business Transitions

In the event Keywordissimo, goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our website of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

##### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

   ©2013 KEYWORDISSIMO. All rights reserved.
